bringtheporn.com 2008-04-26

# Bring the Porn

**Effective July 23, 2007:**

**BringThePorn.com Information**  
BringThePorn.com is an online service that allows our members to create and post content. In order to provide the most enjoyable experience possible for our members, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors. This allows our users to identify each other and communicate and create content to display on our site. It also allows our users to find and communicate with each other. BringThePorn members are able to change how other members communicate and view given profiles by changing account information.

BringThePorn.com cares a great deal about your online privacy If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@bringtheporn.com](mailto:privacy@bringtheporn.com).

**Information Collection and Use by BringThePorn.com**  
BringThePorn.com collects user submitted information such as an email address to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the BringThePorn.com service. 

BringThePorn.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service.

From time to time, BringThePorn.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on BringThePorn.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**Use of Cookies**  
BringThePorn.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from BringThePorn.com in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that BringThePorn allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the BringThePorn Privacy Policy.

**Links**  
BringThePorn.com contains links to other websites. This includes links that are placed there by BringThePorn (such as in advertisements), as well as by other BringThePorn Members. Please be aware that BringThePorn is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage all Members and other users of BringThePorn.com to be aware of when they leave our website, and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by BringThePorn through BringThePorn.com.

**Chat Rooms, Journals and WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and Public Forums**  
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Third Party Advertising**  
Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by BringThePorn.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BringThePorn.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Security**  
BringThePorn.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords BringThePorn.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on BringThePorn.com, please contact us a [privacy@bringtheporn.com](mailto:privacy@bringtheporn.com)

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information BringThePorn.com Collects**  
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, BringThePorn will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by BringThePorn.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the BringThePorn.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. BringThePorn reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of BringThePorn or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so Members and other users of BringThePorn.com are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use Members' or other users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify those Members and users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

**Members and Users Located Outside of the United States of America**  
We have made an effort to protect the personal information of all Members and other users of BringThePorn.com, and to the extent applicable, we attempt to comply with local data protection and consumer rights laws. If you are unsure whether this privacy policy is in conflict with the applicable local rules where you are located, you should not submit your personal information to BringThePorn.com. IN ADDITION, IF YOU ARE LOCATED WITHIN THE EUROPEAN UNION, YOU SHOULD NOTE THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, THE LAWS OF WHICH MAY BE DEEMED BY THE EUROPEAN UNION TO HAVE INADEQUATE DATA PROTECTION (see, for example, European Union Directive 95/46/EC of 24 October 1995). Members and other users of BringThePorn.com located in countries outside of the United States of America who submit personal information do thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that information to and/or storage of the information in the United States of America.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: [privacy@bringtheporn.com](mailto:privacy@bringtheporn.com)

* * *
